const data = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "JavaScript is a ___ -side programming language.",
    answers: ["Client", "Server", "Both", "None"],
    correctAns: "Both",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "Which of the following will write the message “Hello DataFlair!” in an alert box?",
    answers: [
      "alertBox(“Hello DataFlair!”)",
      "alert(Hello DataFlair!);",
      "msgAlert(“Hello DataFlair!”); ",
      "alert(“Hello DataFlair!”);",
    ],
    correctAns: "alert(“Hello DataFlair!”);",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "How do you find the minimum of x and y using JavaScript?",
    answers: [" min(x,y);", " Math.min(x,y)", "Math.min(xy)", "min(xy);"],
    correctAns: "Math.min(x,y)",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which JavaScript label catches all the values, except for the ones specified?",
    answers: ["catch", "label", "try", "default"],
    correctAns: "default",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Which are the correct “if” statements to execute certain code if “x” is equal to 2?",
    answers: ["if(x 2)", "if(x = 2)", "if(x == 2)", " if(x != 2 )"],
    correctAns: "if(x == 2)",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What will the code return?\nBoolean(3 < 7)",
    answers: ["true", "false", "NaN", "SyntaxError"],
    correctAns: "true",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What will the code return?\nBoolean(8 < 7)",
    answers: ["true", "false", "NaN", "SyntaxError"],
    correctAns: "false",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What does CSS stand for?",
    answers: [
      "Creative Style Sheets",
      "Colorful Style Sheets",
      "Computer Style Sheets",
      "Cascading Style Sheets",
    ],
    correctAns: "Cascading Style Sheets",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which of the following selector matches the name of any element type?",
    answers: [
      "The Type Selector",
      "The Universal Selector",
      "The Descendant Selector",
      "The Class Selector",
    ],
    correctAns: "The Universal Selector",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which of the following defines a measurement in inches?",
    answers: ["in", "mm", "pc", "pt"],
    correctAns: "in",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which of the following property is used to control the position of an image in the background?",
    answers: [
      "background-color",
      "background-image",
      "background-position",
      "background-repeat",
    ],
    correctAns: "background-position",
  },
];
